((で　そん中でも　俺 すっげぇ期待されててさぁ))
Bargain x And x Deal The match begins once again.
) ((ひとにレール敷かれる人生 ってやつ))
What is Gon's plan to retake the ball from Razor?
キルア…。
I didn't expect I'd need to use this...
しけた面してんじゃねえぞ　ゴン！
since I've felt this good!
夜が明ければ　パドキア共和国だ。
He threw the ball straight up?
すぐに　キルアに会えるさ。
Does that mean...
うん！
He's going for a spike?
キルアを 絶対に連れ戻すんだ
Hey, over there.
ゴン　レオリオ　クラピカの ３人は キルアが住む　パドキア共和国 デントラ地区へと
I see what you're attempting. Then it's a contest to determine the winner!
見えて来たぜ。
For Hisoka to smother it...
あの山に　暗殺一家のアジトか。
And for Killua to provide support!
一日１本だけど　ガイド付きで あそこから出てるよ。
They did it!
え　本日は
They stopped it! Way to go!
誠に　ありがとうございます。
I have to applaud them for that.
これからバスは　暗殺一族で有名な ゾルディック一家が住む
They overcame my power using their wits.
ククルーマウンテンへと 進んでまいります！
And the key to their success was that boy Killua.
見ろよ！ ん？
Gon focused aura on his
hands to catch the ball.
うん。
The incredible concentration and focus
it took to pull that off deserve my praise.
え　皆様 右手奥をご覧くださいませ！ あちらが　ゾルディック一家が住む ククルーマウンテンでございます。
The moment Gon caught it, Hisoka used his power to smother the ball's
momentum so Gon wouldn't drop it.
樹海に囲まれた　標高３７２２ｍの あの山の　どこかに
Had his technique been less than perfect, the ball would have flown off.
彼らの屋敷があると いわれていますが
And Killua...
いまだ 誰も見た者は　おりません。 そのゾルディック一家は　１０人家族。 曽祖父　祖父　祖母　父　母
He was stuck between them,
acting as both a cushion and a brace, balancing his aura between
offensive and defensive.
その下に５人の兄弟がいて 全員　殺し屋です！ では　もう少しだけ　山に 近づいてみることにしましょう。
If the aura around his body had been too weak, he would have failed to work as a cushion, and all three of them would have taken
major damage from the ball's impact. But if he hadn't used enough aura on his legs, he would have failed to act as a
brace, and the ball would have
こりゃ　すげぇ…。
knocked all three of them outside the court.
こちらが　ゾルディック家の 正門となります。 別名「黄泉への扉」。
He needed to analyze how to balance
入ったら最後　生きて戻れないとの 理由から　そう呼ばれております。
his aura between body and legs
within one-percent accuracy.
中に入るには　守衛室の横にある 扉を使いますが
A feat that demanded both experience and talent.
ここから先は　私有地となって おりますので　見学できません。 おいおい！　正門って…
But Killua managed to compensate for
his inexperience with his prodigious talent, allowing him to overcome such a difficult task.
山は　はるか向こうだぜ！
His talent is scary.
はい ここから先の樹海は　もちろん ククルーマウンテンも全て
I didn't reach that point until
I was in my late twenties...
ゾルディック家の 敷地ということです。
I have to beat them before they can combine.
これが全部　庭ってことかよ。
Right after their attack, my chance will come.
ねぇ　ガイドさん。 はい？ 中に入るには　どうしたらいいの？
If I can get them at that moment,
they won't have time to combine.
ん　坊や 私の説明　聞いてました？ うん　でも　俺…。 中に入れば 二度と生きては出られません！ 殺し屋の隠れ家なのよ。
Certainly, Gon's throw is powerful, but now I have the power to catch
it without being pushed back.
ハッタリだろ？ えっ？ 誰も見たことのない暗殺一家。
Then I can pick them off one at a time.
奴らの顔写真にさえ １億近い懸賞金が かかってるって話だ。
I need more power...
マジか！　クソ！
More...
キルアの写真 撮っときゃよかった！
More!
おら！
He didn't use his full strength earlier?
門を開けな！ 困りますよ。
Unbelievable...
どうせ　あんたのご主人様は 俺達に始末されるんだ。
He's a monster.
あぁ…　ふぅ。
Ging, you should be happy. This kid is definitely your son.
痛てて…。 大丈夫？
Killua, I'm going all-out.
ああ…　大丈夫だよ。
You'd better! If you don't, I'll smack you!
あ　また… ミケが　餌以外の肉　食べちゃうよ。
First comes rock!
ギャ！
Rock, paper...
キャ！ キャ！
However, the momentum will force me out of bounds!
ったく　時間外の食事は 止められてるのにな…。
So catching isn't an option, but I can't dodge, either! Come...
ミケ！　太っても知らないよ！
Trying to receive it again? Fool, that'll let Hisoka grab it!
何だ？　今のは…。 うん。
I wouldn't be so sure... That depends on
ちょっと　あなた達！
the direction in which I direct it!
何やってんの！ 早くバスに乗って！
He bounced it back!
あっ　行っていいですよ。
Gon, dodge!
俺達　ここに残るんで。
You'll still win!
えっ？
No, he won't dodge. That isn't how he wants to win.
なるほどねぇ キルア坊ちゃんの友達ですかい。
He's unconscious? Oh, right.
嬉しいねぇ。
It was the aura he expended...
あたしゃ２０年　勤めてるけど あんた達が初めてだよ。
He truly used every ounce of strength.
友人として ここに来てくれた人はね。
You can take pride in this. You've won, Gon.
雇われの身で　こんなこと言うと 罰が当たりそうだけど
Not quite yet. Why would you do that?!
ホント　寂しいとこだよ。 だれも訪ねて来やしない。
He desired total victory.
Right, Gon?
いや　来てくれて嬉しいよ ありがとう。
He bounced it back again! Interesting.
いやいや。 しかし
Are we just rallying now?
君らを庭内に入れるわけには いかんのです。
It'll come down to stamina!
さっき　君らも見たでしょう デカい生き物の腕を。 あれは　ミケといって
The ball is stuck... Bungee Gum possesses the properties
of both rubber and gum.
忠実に守ってる。 「侵入者は全員　噛み殺せ」 という命令をね。
Razor, catching the ball while touching the
area out of bounds is against the rules. You're out!
いや　忠実じゃないやな 食い殺してるから。
Which makes Team Gon
the winner of this match! All right!
アッハッハッハ…！
That was amazing, guys!
とにかく　中には入れられません。 坊ちゃんの大事な友達を
Huh? What happened at the end?
がい骨にするわけにゃ いかないからねぇ。
They beat me good...
ハハハハ…。
Oh, so Hisoka finished the job.
守衛さん あなたは　なぜ無事なんですか？ ん？
In the end, he stole all the glory.
あなたは　中に入るんでしょう？
It was only possible with all of your help.
中に入る必要がないなら 鍵を持つ必要もないですからね。
Call this a victory for the team. That doesn't sound like you at all.
アッハ…　いいとこ突くねぇ。
You beat me.
でも　半分　当たりで 半分　ハズレです。
As promised, we'll leave the city.
私は入るのに　鍵は使いません。
Oh, yeah... That was this game's purpose.
これは　侵入者用の鍵なんですよ。 侵入者用の鍵？
But first, I will answer your question about Ging.
ああいう連中は　不思議なもんで
Ow!
十中八九 正面から堂々と　やって来る。
Honestly, you were so reckless! Your hands are a total mess. Hey, are you listening?
門を壊してでも 正面から入りたがるんだな
The answer is that Ging isn't here.
迷惑な話ですがね。
Nor do I know where he is.
そこで脇のほうに　わざわざ 鍵付きの扉を設けたんですよ。
Oh... Well, I was expecting that.
侵入者は無抵抗の私から 鍵を奪い
But I can tell you some stories that I know.
ミケに食い殺されるって寸法だ。
Yes, please!
わざわざ鍵付きの… そうか！ フッ。
I, too, was a death row convict.
お察しの通り 私は　守衛じゃ　ない。
I was a murderer.
ミケの 後片付けをする掃除夫です。 そして　本当の門には 鍵が　かかっていない！
I'd been arrested, jailed, and sentenced to die, when Ging hired me to come here.
その通り。 何!?
Ging taught me it took only one person, one person in the entire world who will trust you, to save you.
んん　ん！ フッ！ ん！
Then, I'm counting on you, Razor.
ククク…　ん！
I always thought your old man was insane.
あぁ　うう…　うう…。
He'd spend hours with a death
row convict going on and on
あう　うぉ！
about a game he made, like a kid would.
押しても引いても びくともしねえ！ 鍵　かかってんじゃねえの？
And then he hired that convict
to fight his own son.
単純に力が足らんのですよ。 アホか！ 全力で　やってるっつうの！
Scum! Who do you think is letting you live? Hey... You!
ん？ ん？
Oh, that...
まぁ　ご覧なさい。
Then, I'm counting on you, Razor.
この門さえ開けられないような 輩では…。 フン！
It felt like no one had ever
called me by name before.
ゾルディック家に入る資格なし ってことです。
Ging believed in your strength,
so he left you to me.
ハッ！
And I believed in your strength, which is why I didn't hold back.
う　あっ　ふぅ…。
Yeah, but I couldn't have won
without everyone else.
ご覧の通り 扉は自動的に閉まるから
That was some good teamwork. Yeah.
開いたら　すぐ　中に入ることだね。
Gon, go find Ging.
「試しの門」を開けて 入って来た者は
Yep!
はぁ　しかし　年々これが しんどくなって来てねぇ。
This is the place.
でも　開けられなくなったら クビだから　必死ですよ。
A window? We can see the shore from here.
ちなみに １の扉は　片方２ｔあります。 ２ｔ!? んなもん　動かせねえぞ　普通。
How do we reach the Sea God's Grotto from here?
ええ　ご覧なさい 扉が７まであるでしょ
Directly below the point on the
surface the light points to.
１つ　数が増えるごとに 重さが倍になってるんですよ。
There's a grotto down there.
倍!?
But there isn't any treasure there.
力を入れれば　その力に応じて 大きい扉が開く仕組みなんです。
I'm sorry I deceived you. Really? It's a sacred cavern, so only a few fishermen know the location.
３の扉まで開きましたよ。
All other stories you heard were
rumors made up by others.
３ってことは…　１２ｔ！
Including the stories of treasure.
１６ｔだ　ゴン。 エヘヘ…。 お分かりかね？
But Razor and his gang wouldn't believe us.
敷地内に入るだけで この調子なんだ。 住む世界が違うんです。 うん…　気に入らないな。
Those who make their living on
the sea can never defile it.
おじさん　鍵　貸して。 友達に会いに来ただけなのに 試されるなんて　まっぴらだから
So they said before they were all killed,
taking the secret with them. Hey...
俺は　侵入者でいいよ。
You get that this is a story in a game, right?
だから　鍵を貸して 俺は　侵入者用の扉から入る。 ゴン！ お前…。
I can finally see the ocean again from here.
貸してくれなくても同じだよ 塀をよじ登ってでも中に入るから。
The sunrise... The boats returning with their hauls...
ムチャを言うなよ　ゴン！ さっきの化け物　見ただろ
The water sparkling in many colors.
片腕だけで　お前よりも 数倍　大きかったんだぞ！ だって　納得　行かないよ！ ん？
In my mind, this view is the true treasure.
絶対　そんな扉からは入らない！
Yes! We got Patch of Shore!
確かに 君の言う通りだと思いますよ。
Let's use Clone to make two copies.
しかしね　強行突破は無理ですよ 絶対　ミケに殺される。
We're fine with taking the copies.
私も同感だ　時間はある １の扉から入ることにしよう。
Yes, you've earned the right to the original. Hisoka, you really don't want anything?
ダメだ　こうなっちまったら 聞かねえからな。
Why don't you join us? I'm curious about the Troupe's actions.
確かに…。 うん 残念ですが　鍵は渡せませんや。
I'm not interested in collecting cards.
むざむざ　坊ちゃんの友達を
Should anything else come up,
use Contact to reach me.
ミケの餌食にするわけにゃあ いきませんからね。
I'll use Accompany or Magnetic
Force to come at once.
じゃあ　ちょっと 待っててくださいね。
Huh?
[TEL]
That liar! Huh?
あ　もしもし　ゼブロです。
We haven't used Magnetic Force
at all since Hisoka joined, right?
実はですね　今　ここに キルア坊ちゃんのお友達という方が ３名　みえてるんですが。
That means he already knew about
spell cards before he ran into us!
はい…　はい　すみません はい　はい。 ええ　ええ　分かります はい　すみません　失礼します。
Killua, there are liars who only lie
when there's a reason to, and there are liars who also lie without reason. You and I are the former.
いや やっぱり　叱られちゃったか。
He is the latter.
屋敷に電話してくれたの？
You won't get anywhere by fretting over it.
いや　ゾルディック家の 執事にですがね 屋敷への連絡は 全て　執事に通すんですよ。
Another player has used Contact to reach you. It's been a while.
家族までは　めったに つながらないんです。
Do you know who this is? Genthru?
もう一度かけてくれる？ 今度は　俺が出るから。
What do you want? First, I'd like to congratulate you. What are you talking about?
ええ　いいですけど… 嫌な思いさせちまいますよ。
Don't bother playing dumb.
[TEL]
I promise to spare your lives.
In return, hand over Patch of Shore.
[TEL]　はい　執事室。
Don't be ridiculous.
僕　キルアくんの友達で ゴンといいます。 あの　キルアくん　いますか？
Well, I am somewhat interested
to see if you can beat us.
[TEL]　キルア様に 友達など　おりません。 [TEL]
If you're willing to deal, come alone to Masadora's entrance in one hour. If you don't, we'll take the card by force.
[TEL]
You cannot escape us. We have many copies of Accompany.
[TEL]　はい　執事室。
How?
何で　お前に そんなことが分かるんだ！
I knew he'd find out, but not this soon!
いいから　キルアを出せ！ 君　ゴンくんといったかな？ [TEL]　ああ。
Asta, Amana, Manheim, Nick Cue, Souheil, Kazsule...
[TEL]　仮にキルア様に ゴンという 名前の友人がいるとして
They were all members of
your party of fifteen. Isn't that right?
君がゴンだという保証は どこにもない。
Check your Binder.
キルアを出してくれれば分かる！
They're no longer with us.
[TEL]　声で分かると？ 当てには　ならないね。 [TEL] キルアを出してくれれば分かる！
Book! This means they're either dead
or no longer in the game...
声を似せるだけでいいなら 方法は　いろいろある。
Genthru! Who are you?
次は　「会えば分かる」かな？
Gon Freecss! I'll take you on!
確かに　全身そっくりの偽者を 用意する方法は限られて来るが
Gon? So you're one of those three kids.
それでも不可能ではないし
It appears you have Lucky Alexandrite.
キルア様を狙う人物が
Once I'm done with Tsezgerra, I'll come for you.
ゴン本人を脅して利用する という方法も考えられる。
Or do you want to give up the card now? You come here this instant! I'll fight you!
可能性がある限り キルア様は出せない。
I also have— Tsezgerra, can you move somewhere else?
ゾルディック家は 暗殺をなりわいとしている。 自然　敵も増える。
Another player has used Contact to reach you.
余計な外敵から　あるじを 守るのは　我々　執事の務め。
This is Phinks. We found him. I'm heading your way.
悪いが　お引き取り願おう。 [TEL]
Wouldn't it be faster to target the kids?
おい！　ゴン！
They probably have a copy of Patch of Shore.
ゴン！
But it would be a card created by Clone.
キレてる　キレてる。
That's true.
あいつ…　塀をよじ登る気だな。 何？
Once those kids see Tsezgerra
surrender, they'll give up.
おい！　やめろって　ゴン！ いいよ　２人は待ってて 俺　１人で行くから。
If we go after the kids first, Tsezgerra will have time to recover,
and that will just give us more trouble.
んなわけ　いくか！
He is a Single Star Hunter.
いいから！ よくねえ！
And we don't know what his power is.
冷静になれ　２人とも。 冷静だよ　俺は… 早く下りろ　ゴン！
Genthru doesn't know your strength.
ゴン！　ムチャは　よせ！
So he believes that we are carrying
the original Patch of Shore.
これで　門から　お入りなさい。 待ってくれよ　おっちゃん ゴンは　俺らが説得するから！
They want the original card...
they want "our" card.
そうですか…　でも ゴンくんの意志は固いんでしょ？
We'll try to buy as much time as possible. Use the time to regain your strength.
その代わり　私も 侵入者の門から　ついて行きます。
If you want to beat this game, you'll
have no choice but to fight them.
えっ？ 私が行けば　もしかしたら ミケが　私を覚えていて 攻撃して来ないかもしれません。
And you are the only ones
with a chance to win. But, Gon...
まぁ　ほぼ１００％ 全員　殺されるでしょうが。
Just now, your actions were
both selfish and foolish.
それはダメだよ！ そこまで迷惑は　かけられない。 いいえ　行きます 残っても同じことですから。
If they'd accepted your challenge and come, what would have happened
to Killua, given his injuries?
キルア坊ちゃんの友達を 見殺しにしたら もう　坊ちゃんに 合わせる顔がありません。
You endangered not only yourself, but your friends too, by losing
control of your emotions!
あなた達が死ねば　私も死にます。
I'm sorry. Very well.
分かったよ　おじさん。 おじさんのこと 全然　考えてなかったね　ごめん。
If we evade their use of Accompany,
we should be able to buy plenty of time. But if too much time passes, they may decide to switch and target you.
いい子だ
Past that, we can't make guarantees.
他人のために自分の怒りを 収める優しさを持っている
One week... That isn't long. And that's probably optimistic.
自分の力を信じ それと同じぐらい 仲間を信頼している
They may well switch to us after three days.
芯の強い子だ
I'll go with Tsezgerra.
ミケを見て　物おじしないのは 恐らく…
What about you guys? If we're buying you time,
that implies we have an alliance.
えっ？　うん。
There is little benefit from an alliance with them.
やはりね　ずっと野山を 遊び場にして来たんじゃ ないですか？
The enemy already knows the
eight of us have teamed up.
うん！　何で分かるの？ ゴンくん　もう一度 私が　「試しの門」を開けます。
So we won't be able to act as decoys
while you take out Genthru.
今度は ミケを正面から見てください。
That means leaving the original versions
おい…　俺達も入って平気なのか？
So my offer to buy time isn't an alliance. I'm offering a deal.
ええ 「試しの門」から入れば大丈夫です。
A deal? Three weeks...
ミケ！　おいで！
That's the amount of time we can buy. If we succeed, will you give
us #75, Lucky Alexandrite?
ゴンくん　分かったかな？
That isn't enough time for
Killua's hands to heal.
あれが　完璧に訓練された 狩猟犬ってやつですよ。
And it certainly isn't enough to close the
gap between Genthru's abilities and ours.
君が野山で見て来た どんな野獣とも
Which means we should use the
time to come up with a plan.
全く違う生き物です。
Exactly.
コミュニケーションとれる自信が あったんでしょ？
Devise a scenario in which
you can defeat Genthru.
ミケの目を見るまでは…。 ミケは今　初めて見る人間の姿と においを記憶しています。
Identify the required circumstances,
and prepare to carry out that plan. Got it.
それ以上の感情は 何も持っていません。 機械と同じです。
Good... We'll leave to delay Team Genthru now.
ゴンくん…　こいつと戦えるかい？
Keep this in mind, Gon... They've already killed over
fifty players in this game.
嫌だ　怖い　絶対　戦いたくない。
If you want to beat the game,
you'll have to fight them.
フフ…　本当に素直な子だな
Accompany on!
キルアに会うまで！ それまでは絶対に帰らない！
Three weeks... That isn't much time.
「試しの門」　そして　ミケ
The first necessity is that you be
able to avoid his Little Flower.
ゴンは ゾルディック家の人間が
Osu! Gon has won his match against Razor.
自分達とは全く違う世界に 住んでいることを 目の当たりにした
But the bombers remain stronger
fighters than Gon's group.
それでも ゴンは心に誓っていた
Will they be able to devise a viable plan?